邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
- 爸爸 - 萨姆
- Dad. - Sam?
这比你想象的要大 他们无处不在
This is bigger than you think.They're everywhere.
如果是这个魔鬼杀害了妈妈和杰西的话 爸爸就会在附近
This demon killed Mom and Jess, and Dad's closing in.
- 我们要去帮忙 - 爸爸不要我们帮助
- We gotta help. - Dad doesn't want our help.
我只是想再多待一个星期 来找到答案 去复仇
I'm talking one week here, man.To get answers. To get revenge.
- 你认为我不尊重爸爸 - 抱歉 - 我尊重他
- You think l didn't respect Dad. - Sorry - I brought it up.
无论我做什么都不够优秀
No matter what, it was never good enough.
你说什么 爸爸对你很失望吗
So, what, Dad was disappointed in you?
当我们最终找到爸爸的时候
When we finally do find Dad...
我不知道他是否愿意看到我
l don't know if he's even gonna wanna see me.
- 嘿 爸爸 - 嘿 孩子们
- Hey. Dad?Hey, boys.
- 嗨 萨姆 - 嗨 爸爸
- Hi, Sam. - Hey, Dad.
上次我们见面的时候 我们狠狠的吵了一架
Last time we were together we had one hell of a fight.
- 是的 - 再次见到你真好
- Yes, sir. - lt's good to see you again.
好久不见了
It's been a long time.
我们差点害死爸爸 它们不会就此罢手
We almost got Dad killed in there.They're not gonna stop.
它们还会再试的 它们会利用我们来杀他
They're gonna try again.They're gonna use us to get to him.
当爸爸和我们在一起的时候 他容易被攻击
Dad's vulnerable when he's with us.
- 我要参与战斗 - 萨姆 这场战斗才刚开始
- l gotta be a part of this fight. - Sammy, this fight is just starting.
你必须让我走
You gotta let me go.
(曼宁 科罗拉多 现在)
是埃尔金斯先生吗
Mr. Elkins?
埃尔金斯先生 你还要一杯吗
Mr. Elkins. Would you like another?
是的 谢谢 贝丝
Yeah. Thanks, Beth.
我还以为他们抓到了那个递送邮包炸弹者
Thought they caught the Unabomber.
是的 可怜的埃尔金斯先生 独自一个人住在峡谷里
Yeah, poor Mr. Elkins lives all alone, up the canyon.
每天都坐在这个位置上
Same seat every day.
看他的报纸 记笔记
Going through his papers, and making his little notes.
他是个不错的老人 只是有点神经质
He's a nice old man, he's just a nut.
来了
Here you go.
要点什么？
What will you have?
- 别带瓶子 Jack All Around - 你饿了吗？
- Jack all around. Leave the bottle. - You hungry?
- 我们另有安排 - 好
- We have dinner plans. - Okay.
还要其他的吗埃尔金斯先生
Can l get you something else, Mr. Elkins?
好久不见
It's been a while.
我不得不说 你看起来很苍老
I gotta say, you look old.
你想要干什么 你认为呢
- What do you want? - What do you think?
该死
Damn.
你能干得更好
You can do better than that.
快 快 快
Come-Come on, come on.
好枪
Nice gun.
你当然不会做得很好
Wouldn't do you much good, of course.
男孩们
Boys?
今晚我们开吃吧
We're eating in tonight.
《邪恶力量》
兄弟 整个内华达州都没有什么合适的 你发现什么了吗
Dude, not a decent lead in all of Nebraska. What do you got?
好的 我正在扫描怀俄明州 科罗拉多州和南达科塔
Well, l've been scanning Wyoming, Colorado, South Dakota.
这里 一个爱荷华州的妇女从一万英尺的飞机上掉下来
Here, a woman in lowa fell 10, 000 feet from an airplane
依然活下来了
and survived.
听起来更象是 不可思议 而不是什么灵异事件
Sounds more That's Incredible!than Twilight Zone.
- 没错 - 嘿
- Yeah. - Hey, you know...
不如我们干脆一直往东走
we could just keep heading east.
纽约附近偏僻的地方
New York? Upstate?
可以顺道再去看看莎拉
You could stop by and see Sarah again, huh?
她是个好女孩 兄弟 棒
She's a cool chick, man. Smoking.
你们两个好象关系不错 怎么样
You two seemed pretty friendly.What do you say?
是的 我不知道 也许改天吧
Yeah, l don't know. Maybe someday.But in the meantime...
但是在这期间 我们还有很多工作要做 迪恩 你是知道的
we got a lot of work to do, Dean, and you know that.
是的 你说得对 还找到什么
Yeah, you're right. What else you got?
科罗拉多的一个男人 当地人 叫他丹尼尔·埃尔金斯
Uh, Manning, Colorado. A local man by the name of Daniel Elkins...
- 在他家里被发现血肉模糊 - 埃尔金斯 我听过那个名字
- ...was found mauled in his home. - Elkins? I know that name.
我可没什么印象
- Doesn't ring a bell. - Elkins. Elkins. Elkins.
看来警察一头雾水
The police don't know what to think.
开始他们说是熊干的
At first they said it was some bear attack...
而现在他们又说发现 被抢劫的迹象
and now they found signs of robbery.
恩
Mm-hm.
是的
Yeah.
这里 看一下
There. Check it out.
你认为是同一个埃尔金斯吗？
Think it's the same Elkins?
这是科罗拉多州的地区代码
lt's a Colorado area code.
看起来女仆今天没来
Looks like the maid didn't come today.
嘿 屋内到处是盐
Hey, there's salt here, right inside the door.
你是说象"降伏魔鬼"的盐
You mean like protection-against-demons salt...
还是"我打翻了爆米花"那种盐？
or oops-l-spilled-the-popcorn salt?
明显的 这是个陷阱
It's clearly a ring.
你是说那个埃尔金斯也是捉鬼的人
You think this guy Elkins was a player?
肯定是的
Definitely.
这看起来和爸爸的日记太象了
That looks a hell of a lot like Dad's.
除了这个要回溯到60年代
Yeah, except this dates backto the '60s.
无论是什么攻击了他 看起来都不是一个人干的
Whatever attacked him, it looks like there was more than one.
看起来他也经历了艰苦的战斗
Looks like he put up a hell of a fight too.
是的
Yeah.
找到什么了吗
You got something?
我不知道 地板上有一些抓痕
I don't know. Some scratches in the floor.
也许是垂死挣扎时留下的 也许
- Death throes, maybe? - Yeah, maybe.
或者是某种信号
Or maybe a message.
看起来熟悉吗
Look familiar?
3个字母 6个数字
Three letters, six digits.
组合起来象是邮政信箱
The location and combination of a post office box.
- 这是个邮箱号码 - 和爸爸做事的方法一样
- lt's a mail drop. - lt's just the way Dad does it.
"J. -W. -" 你觉得是 约翰·温彻斯特吗？
"J.W." You think? John Winchester?
我不知道 我们该打开吗？
I don't know. Should we open it?
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸 你在这里干什么？你还好吗？
What are you doing here?Are you all right?
是的 我很好
Yeah, l'm okay.
瞧 我看到了关于丹尼的消息
Look, l read the news about Daniel.
就尽快赶过来
I got here as fast as l could.
我看到你们正好在他的家里
I saw you two up at his place.
- 为什么你不进去 爸爸 - 你知道为什么
- Why didn't you come in, Dad? - You know why.
因为我要确定你们没有被跟踪
Because I had to make sure you weren't followed...
被任何人 任何东西
by anyone or anything.
顺便说下 你们的行踪掩盖得很好
Nice job of covering your tracks, by the way.
是的 我们向最棒的人学的
Yeah, well, we learned from the best.
等等 你不辞辛劳跑来就是为了这个埃尔金斯吗？
Wait, so you came all the way out here for this Elkins guy?
是的
Yeah. He was...
他是 他是个很好的人
He was a good man.
他教了我很多打猎的知识
He taught me a hell of a lot about hunting.
你从没给我们说过他
Well, you never mentioned him to us.
我们
We had a...
我们闹翻了
We had kind of a falling-out.
好几年没见到他了
I hadn't seen him in years.
我要看看那个
I should look at that.
如果你看到这个说明 我已经死了
"If you're reading this, I'm already dead."
- 狗娘养的 - 这是什么
- That son of a bitch. - What is it?
- 原来那东西一直在他那 - 什么 爸爸
- He had it the whole time. - Dad, what?
当你们搜寻这个地方的时候
When you searched the place, did you see a gun?
是否看到一把古董的左轮手枪 你们看到了吗
An antique, a Colt revolver.Did you see it?
那里有个旧盒子 但是是空的
Uh, there was an old case, but it was empty.
- 他们得到了 - 你的意思是什么杀害了埃尔金斯
- They have it. - You mean whatever killed Elkins?
我们必须去看看
We gotta pick up the trail.
- 等等 你要我们陪你去吗 - 如果埃尔金斯说的是事实
- Wait, you want us to come with you? - lf Elkins was telling the truth...
- 我们就必须找到这把枪 - 那把枪 为什么
- ...we've gotta find this gun. - The gun? Why?
因为它很重要 这就是原因
Because it's important, that's why.
我们目前甚至不知道到底是什么鬼怪
We don't know what these things are.
是丹尼尔·埃尔金斯以前最擅长猎杀的…
They were what Daniel Elkins killed best:
吸血鬼
Vampires.
吸血鬼 我还认为他们不存在
Vampires?I thought there was no such thing.
你甚至从没提起过它们 爸爸
You never even mentioned them, Dad.
我以为他们灭绝了
I thought they were extinct.
我以为埃尔金斯和其他人 把他们都铲除了
I thought Elkins and others had wiped them out.
看来我错了
I was wrong.
大多数关于吸血鬼的说法都是错的
Most vampire lore is crap.
十字架不能击败他们 阳光不能杀死他们
A cross won't repel them, sunlight won't kill them...
用树桩插进心脏 也不能杀死他们
and neither Will a stake to the heart.
但是他们嗜血的这部分是真的
but the blood lust, that part's true.
他们靠吸人类新鲜的血生存
They need fresh human blood to survive.
他们曾经是人 所以当你发现他们是吸血鬼的时候
They were once people, so you won't know it's a vampire until
就已经太晚了
it's too late.
全是你的 宝贝
All yours, baby.
什么
What?
- 我猜想你向那个人炫耀了 - 什么人
- Well, l guess you showed that guy. - What guy?
那个打赌你不会买这件衬衫的人
The guy who bet you you wouldn't buy that shirt.
我喜欢这件衬衫
I love this shirt.
小心
No, look out!
- 他怎么样了 - 打911
- What happened to him? - Call 911.
41英里处 有辆废弃的汽车 你要检查吗？
Mile marker 41, abandoned car.You need a Workup?
收到 可能能在这里取证
Copy that. Possible 207.better get Forensics out here.
萨姆 迪恩 我们走
Sam, Dean, let's go.
- 收到一个报警电话 - 发生什么了
- I picked up a police call. - What happened?
一对夫妇打了911 说他们发现一具尸体在路上
A couple called 911, found a body in the street.
警察赶到那里 所有人都不见了 是吸血鬼
Cops got there, everyone was missing.It's the vampires.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
跟我来 好吗
Just follow me, okay?
吸血鬼 每次我听到这个词 就觉得可笑
Vampires.Gets funnier every time l hear it.
我不明白为什么我们 不能和他一起过去
l don't see why we couldn't have gone with him.
哦 别告诉我已经开始了 开始什么了
- Oh, don't tell me it's already starting. - What's starting?
- 发现什么了 - 就是他们 没错
- What do you got? - lt was them, all right.
看起来他们似乎向东去了 我们不得不倒回去
Looks like they're heading west.We have to get
到那些小道上转转
around that detour.
- 你怎么这么肯定 - 萨姆
- How can you be sure? - Sam.
我只想知道我们走的是正确的方向
I just wanna know we're going in the right direction.
- 是正确的 - 你怎么知道
- We are. - How do you know?
我发现这个
I found this.
是什么 吸血鬼的犬牙
It's a vampire fang.
不是犬牙 是獠牙 它们袭击人的时候才会出现的牙齿
No fangs, teeth. A second set descends when they attack.
还有问题吗
Any more questions?
我们离开这里 天快黑了
All right, let's get out of here, we're losing daylight.
迪恩 在车生锈前你为什么不擦擦？
Hey, Dean, why don't you touch up you car before you get rust.
我真不该给你这玩意儿
I wouldn't have given you the damn thing
如果我早知道你会让它生锈
if l thought you were gonna ruin it.
吸血鬼们是8到10个群居
Vampires nest in groups of eight to 10.
年轻的被派出去寻找食物
Smaller packs are sent out to hunt for food.
把战利品活着 带回他们群居的地方
Victims are taken to the nest.
让他们流血 几天到几周
The pack keeps them alive, bleeding them for days or weeks.
我想知道这是否发生在 打911的那对夫妇身上
I wonder if that's what happened to that 911 couple.
那有可能 爸爸怎么看
That's probably what Dad's thinking.
当然 正如他告诉我们的一样
Course, it would be nice if he just told us what he thinks.
果然开始了对吧？
So it is starting.
什么
What?
萨姆 我们一年都在找寻爸爸
Sam, we've been looking for Dad all year.
现在我们还没有和他呆上几个小时 关系就已经这么僵了
We're with him a couple hours and there's static already?
不 听着 我很高兴他安然无恙
No. Look, l'm happy he's okay, all right?
我很高兴我们在一起工作
I'm happy we're all working together again.
好的
Well, good.
他就是这样把我们当小孩看待
It's just the way he treats us like we're children.
他大叫着命令我们 Dean. -
- Oh, God. - He barks orders at us, Dean.
他期望我们什么都不问 只要跟着他就好
He expects us to follow them without question.
他让我们把精力投到那些 需要知道的事情上
He keeps us on some need-to-know deal.
- 他这样做只为一个原因 - 什么原因
- He does what he does for a reason. - What reason?
我们的工作
Our job.
没有时间争辩 没有机会去犯错 老年人都这样做
There's no time to argue, it's just the way the old man runs things.
好的 也许当我们还是孩子的时候还说得过去
Well, maybe that worked when we were kids
现在不行了 好吧
but not anymore.All right?
至少在你和我经历了所有这些事情之后不行了 迪恩
Not after everything you and I have been through.
你别告诉我你就这样心甘情愿当个木偶一样
You telling me you're cool with falling into line
让他操作整件事情
letting him run the whole show?
如果那是成功的必要条件的话
If that's what it takes.
喝点啤酒 朋友 这可以让你平静
Have some beer, buddy.It'll calm your nerves.
- 不 谢谢 - 哦 来吧
- No, thanks. - Oh, come on.
你喝够了 我就能从你血中尝到酒的味道
You drink enough, I can taste it in your blood.
真恶心
That's gross.
那你怎么样 宝贝
How about you, babe?
乖女孩
Attagirl.
- 你 - 博
- You - Bo
等等卢瑟
Wait for Luther.
我也想你 宝贝
I missed you too, baby.
我们有件礼物
We've got presents.
她看起来很有趣
She looks interesting.
他就不是了 把他关起来
He doesn't. Lock him up.
我们走
Let's go.
或者 直接吃了他
On second thought, go ahead and treat yourself.
不
Yeah.
还有样东西
There's something else.
这都是他们的吗 不
- This all theirs? - No.
这是你的一个老朋友的 丹尼尔·埃尔金斯
It's from an old friend of yours, Daniel Elkins
我吻到了他的气味 我想让你惊喜
I caught his scent and l thought l'd surprise you.
凯特 你做了什么
Kate, what did you do?
- 我让他受苦 - 你不该那样做
- l made him suffer. - You shouldn't have done that.
- 卢瑟 - 还有其他象他一样的人
- Luther - There are others like him.
他们知道这个标记 他们会来找我们的 我们不得不小心
They'll know the signs and come looking.We have to be careful.
卢瑟 我是为你做的 为了他对你家人所做的一切
I did it for you, for what he did to your family.
要是你可能因此被杀死的话 这种复仇就是不值得的
Revenge isn't worth much if you end up dead.
对不起 宝贝 对不起
I'm sorry, babe. I'm sorry.
我以为你会喜欢的
I thought you might like that.
看起来是在你出生的年代制造的
Looks like it was made around the time you were born.
- 我以前见过这个 - 埃尔金斯死时拿着它
- l've seen this before. - Elkins died with it in his hands.
他真该好好练习怎么用枪
He should've known better, using a gun.
这不是普通的枪
This is no ordinary gun.
知道了 爸爸 好的
Yeah, Dad. All right, got it.
- 下个出口停下 - 为什么
- Pull off the next exit. - Why?
- 因为爸爸觉得已经找到了吸血鬼的行踪 - 怎么找到的？
- Dad thinks we've got the vampires' trail. - How?
我不知道 他没有说
I don't know. He didn't say.
- 哦 天啊 又来了 萨姆 - 这是怎么了
Ah, crap. Here we go. Sam! - What the hell was that?
- 我们需要谈谈 - 谈什么
We need to talk-About what?
所有事情
About everything.
我们到哪里去 爸爸 这把枪有什么大不了的
Where are we going?What's the big deal about this gun?
我们可以再杀了所有的吸血鬼后再解决这事
We can q and a after we kill all the vampires.
- 我们没有多少时间了 - 上次我见你
- We don't have time for this. - Last time we saw you...
你说在一起太危险 现在 突然你又需要我们的帮助
it was too dangerous to be together. Now you need our help.
很显然有什么大事情发生了 我们想知道是什么
Something big is going down and we wanna know what.
- 回到车上去 - 不
- Get back in the car. - No.
- 我说回到该死的车上去 - 好 我的回答是 不
- l said, get back in the damn car. - Yeah, and l said no.
好的 你已经表明了观点 混小子
You made your point, tough guy.
你看 我们都很累了 我们可以晚点再谈
We're tired, we can talk about this later.
- 你说什么 - 你知道我在说什么
- What'd you say? - You heard me.
是的 你离开了
Yeah. You left.
抛下你哥哥和我 我们需要你的时候
Your brother and me, we needed you.
- 你就那样走了 萨姆 就那么走了
- You walked away. Sam.You walked away.
听下 你们俩
Stop it, both of you.
是你叫我不要再回来的 爸爸
You're the one who said, "Don't come back."
是你关上了门 不是我
You're the one who closed that door.
你是因为不能再控制我了才发彪的
You were just pissed off you couldn't control me anymore.
停下 停下 停下 够了
Listen. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.That's enough.
那也在说你
That means you too.
真是太好了
Terrific.
你喜欢看 是吗
You like to watch, huh?
我也是
Me too.
准备好了吗 宝贝
Ready, baby?
你们会杀了我吗
Are you gonna kill me?
我会让你爽翻天 如坠云间的
I'm gonna take you so high, you're never gonna come down.
欢迎成为我们一份子 宝贝
Welcome home, baby.
我知道时间
I know what time it is.
进来
Get in.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
所以说他们是真的不怕阳光
So they're really not afraid of the sun?
不 直接日照只会晒黑
Direct sunlight hurts like a nasty sunburn.
唯一的方法是把他们的头砍下来
The only way to kill them is by beheading.
还有 他们白天睡觉
And yeah, they sleep during the day.
但并不是说他们不会醒
Doesn't mean they won't wake up.
所以我想直接进去不是最好的方法
So l guess walking right in is not our best option.
实际上 就这么干
Actually, that's the plan.
爸爸 如果你需要的话 我有额外的刀
Hey, Dad. l've got an extra machete if you need one.
没事 谢了
Think l'm okay, thanks.
哦
Wow.
那么
So...
你们真的想了解这把枪吗
You boys really wanna know about this Colt?
是的
Yes, sir.
这是个故事 一个传说 真的
It's just a story. A legend, really.
是的 我也那么觉得
Well, l thought it was.
在读丹尼尔的信以前 我从来都不相信
I never really believed it until I read Daniel's letter.
在1835年 当时哈雷彗星出现在天上
back in 1835, when Halley's Comet was overhead...
同时也是那些人在白杨树下死去的那晚
the same night those men died at the Alamo...
他们说塞缪尔·柯尔特制造了这把枪
they say Samuel Colt made a gun.
特别的枪
A special gun.
这是一把为猎人打造的枪
He made it for a hunter.A man like us, only on horseback.
一个和我一样的人 传说他造了13颗子弹
The story goes, he made 13 bullets.
这个猎人使用这把枪
This hunter used the gun a half dozen times...
在他消失前 这把枪一直跟随他
before he disappeared, the gun along with him.
不知何故 丹尼尔得到了它
Until somehow, Daniel got his hands on it.
他们说
They say...
他们说这把枪能杀死任何东西
They say this gun can kill anything.
任何东西？超自然的东西也行吗？
Kill anything, like supernatural anything?
例如魔鬼
Like the demon.
是的 魔鬼
Yeah, the demon.
每次我发现它们的踪迹
Ever since I picked up its trail...
我都要找个方法杀死它们
l've been looking for a way to destroy that thing.
找到这把枪
Find the gun...
我们可以使用它
we may have it.
迪恩
Dean
这边还有
There's more.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 我是来帮助你的
Hey, hey. Shh. I'm here to help you.
不
No!
萨姆
Sam!
孩子们 快跑
Boys, run!
爸爸
Dad!
Dad?
爸爸
Dad!
他们不会跟来 他们会等到黑夜来临
They won't follow. They'll wait till night.
一旦吸血鬼记住了你的气味 你就跑不掉了
Once a vampire gets your scent, it's for life.
我们现在怎么做 你们尽快找到一家最近的殡仪馆
- What the hell do we do? - You gotta find the nearest funeral home.
怎么这么久 我应该去帮忙
It shouldn't be taking this long.I should go help.
迪恩会搞定的
Dean's got it.
萨姆
Sammy
什么
Yeah?
我没有告诉过你这些
I never told you this...
但是你知道在你出生那天 我做了什么吗？
but the day you were born, you know what l did?
- 不 - 我为你开了个
- No. - l put a hundred bucks...
100美元的帐户
into a savings account for you.
我为你哥哥做了同样的事情
I did the same thing for your brother.
那是读大学的基金
It was a college fund.
然后每个月 我都会存进100块 直到…
And every month, I'd put in another $100 until...
总之 我的意思是 萨姆
Anyway, my point is, Sam...
这从来不是我想你过的生活
that this was never the life that l wanted for you.
那在我离开的时候 你为什么那么生气
Then why did you get so mad when l left?
你应该明白
You gotta understand something.
在你母亲去世后
After your mother passed...
我所接触的都是些鬼怪 到处都是
all l saw was evil. Everywhere.
我所关心的是要
And all l cared about was
让你们兄弟两个好好活着
Was keeping you boys alive.
我希望你
I wanted you...
能有所准备
prepared.
任何时候都有所准备
Ready.
所以在这个过程中…
See, somewhere along the line, I
我不再是你父亲的角色
I stopped being your father...
而是 成为了你的训练官
and l-l became your-Your drill sergeant.
当你说你要离开去上学的时候
So when you said that you wanted to go away to school...
我仅仅能想到的
all l could think about, my only thought...
就是你只有一个人
was that you were gonna be alone.
脆弱而危险
Vulnerable.
萨姆 只是 只是我从来没想到过你到底要什么
Sammy, it just It never occurred to me what you wanted.
我只是不能接受事实 你和我 我们是不一样的
I just couldn't accept the fact that you and me, we're just different.
什么
What?
我们没有什么不同
We're not different.
不再有
Not anymore.
发生了妈妈和杰西的事后
With what happened to Mom and Jess...
我们大概拥有 比任何人都多的共同点
we probably have a lot more in common than just about anyone.
我想你是对的 儿子
I guess you're right, son.
嘿 爸爸
Hey, Dad?
大学基金怎么了
Whatever happened to that college fund?
花在武器上了
Spent it on ammo.
哇
Whew.
保护些死人还要那么多保安措施
Man, some heavy security to protect a bunch of dead guys.
你拿到了吗
You get it?
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
车有问题吗
Car trouble?
我搭你去 带你回我的地方
Let me give you a lift, take you back to my place.
不了 我可得和恋尸狂划清界限
I'll pass. I usually draw the line at necrophilia.
通常要到第二次约会我才会象你这么友好
I don't normally get this friendly till the second date, but...
你知道 我们可以找点乐子
You know, we could have some fun.
我总是喜欢交新朋友
I always like to make new friends.
哦 对不起
Sorry.
我从来没有和一个女人呆这么长时间 显然再也不会了
Don't really stay with a chick that long.Definitely not eternity.
该死的
Damn it.
无关痛痒
Barely even stings.
别心急 甜心
Give it time, sweetheart.
箭浸了死人的血
Arrow's soaked in dead man's blood.
对你来说是毒药 是不是
It's like poison to you, isn't it?
把她关起来 我来对付这个
Load her up. l'll take care of this one.
那这些投进火里 藏红花 臭鼬皮 甘蓝 和延龄草
Toss this on the fire.Saffron, skunk's cabbage and trillium.
在我们准备好以前 这会盖住我们和她的气味
It'll block our scent, and hers, until we're ready.
- 这真臭 - 就是这个意思
- Stuff stinks. - That's the idea.
拍掉身上的灰 你们就有机会不被发现
Dust your clothes with the ashes and you might not be detected.
你确定他们会来找她吗
You sure they'll come after her?
是的 吸血鬼很团结
Yeah. Vampires mate for life.
对为首的来说 她比枪重要
She means more to the leader than the gun.
不过这个血液疾病会很快消失
But the blood-sickness is gonna wear off soon...
所以你们时间不多
so you don't have a lot of time.
半小时应该够了
Half-hour ought to do it.
然后我想你们要尽量远离这一带 但是
- Then l want you out of the area fast. - But
你一个人不能对付他们全部
Dad, you can't take care of them all.
我有她和枪
I'll have her. And the Colt.
过后 我们再见面 好吗
But after, we're gonna meet up, right?
一起用这把枪
Use the gun together.
对吗
Right?
你是不是要再次离开
You're leaving again, aren't you?
你仍然想一个人追逐那个恶魔？
You still wanna go after the demon alone.
你知道 我不理解你
You know, I don't get you.
- 你不能这样对待我们 - 不能怎样
- You can't treat us like this. - Like what?
- 象对待孩子一样 - 你们是我的孩子
- Like children. - You are my children.
我想让你们安全
I'm trying to keep you safe.
爸爸 无意冒犯 那些都是些鬼话
Dad, all due respect, but that's a bunch of crap.
- 你说什么？- 你知道萨姆和我是怎样猎杀恶鬼的
- Excuse me? - You know what we've been hunting.
有些猎物还是你叫我们去的
Hell, you sent us on a few hunting trips yourself.
- 你不必那样担心我们的安全 - 这次不一样
- You can't be that worried about us. - lt's not the same thing.
那是什么？你为什么让我们远离这么重要的战斗？
Then what is it? Why do you want us out of the big fight?
这些魔鬼
This demon...
都很厉害
it's a bad son of a bitch.
如果我要担心你们的安全的话 我就没有办法做事
I can't make the same moves if l worry about keeping you alive.
你不能这样不计后果
You can't be as reckless.
听我说
Look...
我不希望单一的看待这场战斗
l don't expect to make it out of this in one piece.
你们母亲的死
Your mother's death...
让我伤痛欲绝
it almost killed me.
我不能再看着我的孩子死去 我也不会让它发生
I can't watch my children die too.I won't.
要是你死了我们怎么办
What happens if you die?
爸爸 你死了我们该怎么办
What happens if you die and we could've done something about it?
我们该做些什么呢 我在想
You know, I've been thinking. I...
我想也许萨姆在这件事上是对的
Maybe Sammy's right about this one.
我认为我们应该一起干这件事情
We should do this together.
我们一家人团结起来就更强大 爸爸 你是知道这个的
We're stronger as a family.We just are. You know it.
我们快没有时间了
We're running out of time.
你们做你们的事情 离开这里
You do your job and you get out of the area.
那是命令
That's an order.
- 有那3个人的踪迹吗 - 没有 有其他的事情
- Any sign of those three? - No. Something else.
- 什么 - 卢瑟 他们砍了汉克的头
- What? - Luther, they cut off Hank's head!
凯特呢
And Kate?
我不知道 她不在那里
I don't know. She wasn't there.
我们现在做什么
What are we gonna do?
公路上有辆卡车
Just a truck, up on the highway.
凯特
Kate
她在卡车里
She's in that truck.
我说过我会回来的
I told you l'd come back.
下车
Get out.
- 你是谁 - 我叫温彻斯特
- Who are you? - Name's Winchester.
- 你朋友在哪里 - 清理你们的窝去了
- Where are your friends? - Cleaning out your nest.
凯特在哪里
Where's Kate?
过来 甜心
Come here, sweetheart.
凯特 你没事吧？
Kate, you all right?
死人的血
Dead man's blood.
狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
我要埃尔金斯的枪 作为交易
I want the Colt, Elkins' gun. A trade.
就是这些吗 我是说 你不能同时对付我们全部
Is that what this is about? I mean, you can't shoot us all.
我们会杀了你的
We'll kill you.
哦 不是用来对付你们的
Oh, l don't need it for you.
我有其他用途
I'm saving it for something else.
现在 把枪放下 我就放了她
Put the Colt down or she goes first.
好的
All right.
别伤害她
Just don't hurt her.
退后
Back up.
再远点
Further.
干得不错 差点就能成功了
It's a nice move. You almost made it.
别动 不然我就拧断他的脖子 把刀放下
Nope. I'll break his neck.Put the blade down.
你们
You people.
为什么不能放过我们
Why can't you just leave us alone?
- 我们和你们一样有生存的权利 - 我可不那么认为
- We have as much right to live as you do. - I don't think so.
卢瑟
Luther!
凯特 不要
Kate, don't!
孩子们
So, boys...
什么
Yes, sir?
你们违抗命令回来
You ignored a direct order back there.
- 是的 - 但是我们救了你的命
- Yes, sir. - Yeah, but we saved your ass.
没错
You're right.
- 是吗 - 你吓死我了
- l am-lt scares the hell out of me.
你们是我的所有
You two are all I've got...
我猜想我们在一起会更强大
but l guess we are stronger as a family.
那么 我们追逐这些邪恶的东西
So we go after this damn thing.
一起去
Together.
是
Yes sir.